<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

  <channel>
    <title>Staybazar Blog</title>
    <atom:link href="https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <link>https://www.staybazar.com/blog</link>
    <description>The Alternative Stay Option</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 17:12:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
    <sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
    <generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.4.2</generator>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Unbelievable offer at Ocean Spray, Pondicherry</title>
      <link>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/02/17/unbelievable-offer-at-ocean-spray-pondicherry/</link>
      <comments>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/02/17/unbelievable-offer-at-ocean-spray-pondicherry/#respond</comments>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 05:46:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <dc:creator><![CDATA[StayBazar]]></dc:creator>
      <category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.staybazar.com/blog/?p=14</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Property: Ocean Spray, Pondicherry (5 Star Property) Offer Period: 12 Feb through 29 Feb 2016 Stay Period: 12 Feb through 31 Mar 2016 Offer: Book for one night on APAI and avail second night stay complimentary. Price: 11,800 INR Inclusions: Double occupancy accommodation for one night, one breakfast, lunch and dinner for both guests Terms: [&#8230;]]]></description>
      <content:encoded>
        <![CDATA[<p>Property: Ocean Spray, Pondicherry (5 Star Property)</p>
<p>Offer Period: 12 Feb through 29 Feb 2016<br />
Stay Period: 12 Feb through 31 Mar 2016<span class="text_exposed_show"><br />
Offer: Book for one night on APAI and avail second night stay complimentary.<br />
Price: 11,800 INR<br />
Inclusions: Double occupancy accommodation for one night, one breakfast, lunch and dinner for both guests<br />
Terms: Second night stay complimentary on EPAI basis, available only on Fern category rooms.</span></p>
<div class="text_exposed_show">
<p>Book your stay today!</p>
</div>
<p>Call us now 080-2570-2898 / 098801-88880 or email us at info@staybazar.com</p>
]]>
      </content:encoded>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/02/17/unbelievable-offer-at-ocean-spray-pondicherry/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
    </item>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Reasons Traveling Makes You a Better Person</title>
      <link>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/02/05/5-reasons-traveling-makes-you-a-better-person/</link>
      <comments>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/02/05/5-reasons-traveling-makes-you-a-better-person/#respond</comments>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 05:54:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <dc:creator><![CDATA[StayBazar]]></dc:creator>
      <category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.staybazar.com/blog/?p=18</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Traveling connects you to the world in mysterious ways. It reminds you of the ground beneath your feet and the sky above your head. When it comes to the big picture, nothing comes closer than packing your bags and heading out to see it for yourself. Here’s a run down on the top five reasons [&#8230;]]]></description>
      <content:encoded>
        <![CDATA[<p>Traveling connects you to the world in mysterious ways. It reminds you of the ground beneath your feet and the sky above your head. When it comes to the big picture, nothing comes closer than packing your bags and heading out to see it for yourself. Here’s a run down on the top five reasons we love to travel &#8211;</p>
<ol>
<li>You get out of your comfort zone</li>
</ol>
<p>Living in the city means you have to get used to a routine. From the minute you wake up, you know what needs to be done for the rest of the day. You’ve already decided your outfit for the day, rehearsed your meetings and presentations, have a special spot at your local bar and order the same thing every time. It’s just the way it is. Traveling breaks old habits and gives you space to breathe while inviting change.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>You make new friends</li>
</ol>
<p>Having a friend circle is great when you’re in the hood but when you’ve arrived at your destination, you end up meeting and greeting new faces. It could be the cute girl at the counter, the homestay owner or someone you bump into, they’re all just a hello away from becoming your new friends.</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>You gain experiences</li>
</ol>
<p>Some of the wealthiest people in the world invest their money on experiences because at the end of the day, you’re more than just the stuff you own. Being on the move reminds you of that and makes you explore the world with childlike eyes of wonder and excitement.</p>
<ol start="4">
<li>You learn more about the world</li>
</ol>
<p>The world is like a book and those who don’t travel read only a page. The world is bigger than the serviced apartment you rent and many interesting people are waiting to meet you and make you a part of their story. Every place has its own unique culture and traveling gives you an insight into the unknown. Remember, there are no strange places, just new ones.</p>
<ol start="5">
<li>You learn more about yourself</li>
</ol>
<p>It is on journeys taken far and wide that you discover your hidden potential. Anything can happen while you’re traveling and each moment reveals a unique part of you, like pieces of a puzzle. Maybe you’ll find that you don’t like cream in your coffee or find out how soothing a walk on the beach can be. These little incidents can become the most cherished treasures you’ll uncover and traveling is the way to do it.</p>
<p>If you’re finally convinced, then get off your behind and get on the road!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>About StayBazar</strong></p>
<p>Staybazar.com is an online market place for various alternate stay options. Staybazar has a robust technological platform offering a wide range of alternate stay options to our individual, family and corporate customers and the offering ranges from Serviced Apartments, Resorts, Homestays, Theme stays, etc.</p>
<p>Stay Bazar customers can search and book homely stay options of their choice for shorter to longer duration from the convenience of their home or office by logging on staybazar.com. No more worry of compromising yourself to a cramped hotel room while on your personal or business travel.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]>
      </content:encoded>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/02/05/5-reasons-traveling-makes-you-a-better-person/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Travel Destinations in India</title>
      <link>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/02/01/top-5-travel-destinations-in-india/</link>
      <comments>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/02/01/top-5-travel-destinations-in-india/#respond</comments>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 05:57:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <dc:creator><![CDATA[StayBazar]]></dc:creator>
      <category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.staybazar.com/blog/?p=21</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Rich with natural resources and beautiful landscapes, India is a diverse land that offers a wealth of experiences for travelers from around the world. If its your first time traveling in India and you are itching to plan your next trip, we’ve got just the thing for you. Be sure to hit these towns on [&#8230;]]]></description>
      <content:encoded>
        <![CDATA[<p>Rich with natural resources and beautiful landscapes, India is a diverse land that offers a wealth of experiences for travelers from around the world. If its your first time traveling in India and you are itching to plan your next trip, we’ve got just the thing for you. Be sure to hit these towns on your way to get a taste of the true flavour this great nation.</p>
<p><strong>Bangalore</strong></p>
<p>Known as the Silicon Valley of India, Bangalore has gained a reputation for being a metropolitan in the true sense. The city is bustling with theatre plays, counter-culture performances, WiFi enabled zones and the most number of pubs you’ll ever find. People book serviced apartments in this tech town to have their share of artistic ambitions while living the big city life.</p>
<p><strong>Mumbai</strong></p>
<p>Mumbai is the city that never sleeps. From A-list Bollywood bashes to street side vada pavs, you can get whatever you want and whenever you want it. The food tastes heavenly and costs well under your budget but the real estate is quite expensive. That’s the only downside to this live wire of a city but it is also the place where Indian dreams come true.</p>
<p><strong>Goa</strong></p>
<p>Goa is the party capital of India. It is surrounded by plenty of beaches, each with its own unique vibe. Take a banana boat ride at the beach, eat delicious sea food, sing at the karaoke bar or just unwind at little shacks spread across the shore. It also has beautiful churches with a culture that celebrates life in any way it can.</p>
<p><strong>Jaipur</strong></p>
<p>Popularly called the Pink City, Jaipur is an architectural jewel like no other. It is one-third of the Golden Triangle of Indian tourism. Hotel and resorts can cut a hole in your pocket so finding alternative stay options is your best bet. Visitors can find plenty of attractions such as  Hawa Mahal, Jal Mahal, City Palace, Amer Fort, Jantar Mantar, Nahargarh Fort, Galtaji and Govind Dev Ji Temple among others.</p>
<p><strong>Agra</strong></p>
<p>Situated on the banks of river Yamuna, Agra is home to one of the Wonders of the World, The Taj Mahal. Agra, Jaipur and Delhi form the Golden Triangle of Indian tourism. The city has a rich culture of arts dating back to the Mughal era and masterpieces can be found anywhere in the vicinity. Other attractions include the Agra Fort, Fatehpur Sikri, Akbar’s Tomb and the Keetham lake.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Come back for more travel destinations when you’ve crossed these five off your list. Until then, keep traveling!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>About StayBazar</strong></p>
<p>Staybazar.com is an online market place for various alternate stay options. Staybazar has a robust technological platform offering a wide range of alternate stay options to our individual, family and corporate customers and the offering ranges from Serviced Apartments, Resorts, Homestays, Theme stays, etc.</p>
<p>Stay Bazar customers can search and book homely stay options of their choice for shorter to longer duration from the convenience of their home or office by logging on staybazar.com. No more worry of compromising yourself to a cramped hotel room while on your personal or business travel.</p>
]]>
      </content:encoded>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/02/01/top-5-travel-destinations-in-india/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Things to Carry While Traveling</title>
      <link>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/01/30/5-things-to-carry-while-traveling/</link>
      <comments>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/01/30/5-things-to-carry-while-traveling/#respond</comments>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2016 06:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <dc:creator><![CDATA[StayBazar]]></dc:creator>
      <category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.staybazar.com/blog/?p=27</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[When the world is filled with wonder and beauty, it’s only natural to want to go out there and see it for yourself. If you are an avid traveler with a sense of adventure, you need to pack light while you are on your journey. Keeping your luggage to a bare minimum is essential to [&#8230;]]]></description>
      <content:encoded>
        <![CDATA[<p>When the world is filled with wonder and beauty, it’s only natural to want to go out there and see it for yourself. If you are an avid traveler with a sense of adventure, you need to pack light while you are on your journey. Keeping your luggage to a bare minimum is essential to make the most of your endeavours. Just tick these things off your checklist and you should be good to go &#8211;</p>
<ol>
<li>Best outfits</li>
</ol>
<p>When you are out visiting, it’s always good to dress your very best. Meeting new people on trips is an imperative and making an impression can go a long way in making your stay worthwhile. Be it for business or leisure, your favourite outfits are known to bump up your luck at home and can do wonders when you are away.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>Cash and cards</li>
</ol>
<p>If you’re going to an offbeat destination for your holiday, make sure you carry some hard cash with you at all times. Living at an alternative stay away from the hustle and bustle of the city means banks and ATMs may be off the radar for miles at a stretch. Smaller shops that serve tea and sell other condiments don’t accept cards as payment.</p>
<ol start="3">
<li>Daily dose</li>
</ol>
<p>It goes without saying that health is a priority, wherever you go. Secure your daily doses of medicine by packing them in ziplock bags. Prescription drugs are hard to come by and missing out on yours when you need them is the last thing you need on a vacation.</p>
<ol start="4">
<li>Appsolutely necessary</li>
</ol>
<p>Smart phones have made things convenient for people everywhere. Internet connectivity and GPS can come in handy on tour, especially when you want to book your resort on the go. Check the App Store with your travel destination and you’ll be surprised by what comes up. For instance, search for Goa and you’ll know exactly what we’re talking about.</p>
<ol start="5">
<li>Toiletry</li>
</ol>
<p>Last but not least, pack all your toiletries like toothbrush, sunscreen, deodorant and other supplies before you leave. Remember, the products you use aren’t always available on the shelves which makes your belongings all the more valuable.</p>
<p>Traveling can be an enriching experience only when you do it right. The next time you step out, make sure you have these five pre-requisites to have a great trip.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>About StayBazar</strong></p>
<p>Staybazar.com is an online market place for various alternate stay options. Staybazar has a robust technological platform offering a wide range of alternate stay options to our individual, family and corporate customers and the offering ranges from Serviced Apartments, Resorts, Homestays, Theme stays, etc.</p>
<p>Stay Bazar customers can search and book homely stay options of their choice for shorter to longer duration from the convenience of their home or office by logging on staybazar.com. No more worry of compromising yourself to a cramped hotel room while on your personal or business travel.</p>
]]>
      </content:encoded>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/01/30/5-things-to-carry-while-traveling/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dream Destinations for Valentine&#8217;s Day!!</title>
      <link>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/01/29/valentines-month/</link>
      <comments>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/01/29/valentines-month/#respond</comments>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 11:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <dc:creator><![CDATA[StayBazar]]></dc:creator>
      <category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.staybazar.com/blog/?p=1</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Book your stay now at staybazar.com or talk to us on our toll free number:  1800-425-2393. You could also write to us at support@staybazar.com &#160; VALENTINE&#8217;S DAY CONTEST: Winners get to choose from 11 locations so put your heart in it. Share your magic moments of love with us on our facebook page and you could win an unforgettable two [&#8230;]]]></description>
      <content:encoded>
        <![CDATA[<p><img class="size-full wp-image-10 aligncenter" src="https://www.staybazar.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/staybazar_destinations2.png" alt="staybazar_destinations2" width="760" height="2714" srcset="https://www.staybazar.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/staybazar_destinations2-84x300.png 84w, https://www.staybazar.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/staybazar_destinations2.png 760w" sizes="(max-width: 760px) 100vw, 760px" /></p>
<p>Book your stay now at <a href="http://www.staybazar.com">staybazar.com</a> or talk to us on our toll free number:  1800-425-2393. You could also write to us at <a href="mailto:support@staybazar.com" target="_blank">support@staybazar.com</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>VALENTINE&#8217;S DAY CONTEST:</p>
<p>Winners get to choose from 11 locations so put your heart in it. Share your magic moments of love with us on our facebook page and you could win an unforgettable two night free stay for a couple at a dream destination this Valentine’s Day.</p>
<p><strong>T&amp;Cs</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>The winner will win a 2 nights stay at any one of the above mentioned 11 locations in stay options provided by Stay Bazar.</li>
<li>The prize is non-transferable.</li>
<li>All contestants must be above 21 years of age and must carry a valid photo ID.</li>
<li>Multiple entries are allowed.</li>
<li>All campaign entries must be submitted before 12 Feb, 2016. The winner will be announced on the 14 Feb, 2016.</li>
<li>Stay voucher should be redeemed before 31 March, 2016.</li>
<li>Winning couple will be hosted on twin-sharing basis with accommodation and breakfast paid by Staybazar.</li>
<li>StayBazar has the ultimate judgement over winners and the decision is not up for review.</li>
</ul>
]]>
      </content:encoded>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/01/29/valentines-month/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bestie in Bangalore!</title>
      <link>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/01/19/bestie-in-bangalore/</link>
      <comments>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/01/19/bestie-in-bangalore/#respond</comments>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 06:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <dc:creator><![CDATA[StayBazar]]></dc:creator>
      <category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.staybazar.com/blog/?p=24</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[Deepak and I have known each other our entire lives. We went to the same school together. We partied together. We pulled each other’s legs and stood up for each other throughout and now just because his dad wants him to do engineering, he is shifting to Bangalore. Separation Anxiety You know how on somedays [&#8230;]]]></description>
      <content:encoded>
        <![CDATA[<p>Deepak and I have known each other our entire lives. We went to the same school together. We partied together. We pulled each other’s legs and stood up for each other throughout and now just because his dad wants him to do engineering, he is shifting to Bangalore.</p>
<p>Separation Anxiety</p>
<p>You know how on somedays you accidentally sleep on your hand and wake up without feeling it and freak out. That’s how I felt the day after Deepak left. Suddenly, I didn’t have my wing man at the bar, so no more dates. I didn’t have my chaddi dost to just hang out and kill time everyday. As the days went by I got used to his absence but hey, I’m not the kind who forgets his mates so I wanted to pay my old friend a visit.</p>
<p>Silicon Valley of India</p>
<p>I had never been to Bangalore but I planned on doing it soon. You see, next week is Deepak’s birthday and I’m throwing him a little surprise. I’ve got the whole thing chalked out. I booked a serviced apartment in Banashankari so it’s close to his college hostel. The internet can really come in handy when you want to plan things in a new city. I’m bringing the A team with me, our best buds Srikar and Soumya agreed to tag along for the big day.</p>
<p>Home away from home</p>
<p>The whole crew had come down to Bangalore a couple of days ahead of Deepak’s birthday so we could make our alternative stay look like his room from our home town. We wanted him to feel like he had come back home for his special day and I think we pulled it off. It was perfect. All we needed to do now was wait.</p>
<p>A few hours before the clock hit 12, I texted Deepak the address and asked him to come there before midnight. He kept calling me and I kept cutting the call. I texted him again to confirm I wasn’t kidding. It was 11.30pm when he walked in.</p>
<p>“SURPRISE!”</p>
<p>“What the fish! When did you guys get here? Did you move all my stuff here? Oh my god!” he said.</p>
<p>I took a picture on his face when he walked in so we can never forget it. He was ecstatic and so were we. I told him the whole story over a few drinks and he couldn’t believe someone would go through all that trouble for him. And I told him</p>
<p>“I’d do it all over again bud, cheers, happy birthday to my bestie in Bangalore!”</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>About StayBazar</strong></p>
<p>Staybazar.com is an online market place for various alternate stay options. Staybazar has a robust technological platform offering a wide range of alternate stay options to our individual, family and corporate customers and the offering ranges from Serviced Apartments, Resorts, Homestays, Theme stays, etc.</p>
<p>Stay Bazar customers can search and book homely stay options of their choice for shorter to longer duration from the convenience of their home or office by logging on staybazar.com. No more worry of compromising yourself to a cramped hotel room while on your personal or business travel.</p>
]]>
      </content:encoded>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/01/19/bestie-in-bangalore/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I am a Traveler</title>
      <link>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/01/17/i-am-a-traveler/</link>
      <comments>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/01/17/i-am-a-traveler/#respond</comments>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 06:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <dc:creator><![CDATA[StayBazar]]></dc:creator>
      <category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.staybazar.com/blog/?p=30</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[I am a traveler. I travel to find my home away from home. I travel to find my friends who I haven’t met yet. I travel to learn, about myself and the world. It’s not just about moving from one place to another. It’s about blending with people and places you’ve never seen before. Adventure [&#8230;]]]></description>
      <content:encoded>
        <![CDATA[<p>I am a traveler. I travel to find my home away from home. I travel to find my friends who I haven’t met yet. I travel to learn, about myself and the world. It’s not just about moving from one place to another. It’s about blending with people and places you’ve never seen before.</p>
<p><strong>Adventure abound</strong></p>
<p>As a boy looking over the oceans, I dreamt that one day I would venture across the seven seas. So much beauty and so little time. City life can be gruelling and sometimes it makes us forget the things that are truly important. Traveling helps me come out of my comfort zone. When I’m on the road, each step I take leads to a fresh experience. I maybe sharing a room at an alternative stay on the beach or hitch a ride on a rugged motorcycle, I never know what comes next and that’s what keeps me going.</p>
<p><strong>Faces and phases</strong></p>
<p>They say that the world is a book and those who don’t travel read only a page. I couldn’t agree more. From moment to moment, there’s always a chance to meet a new face in a mysterious place. With stay options available at my fingertips, accommodation is the least of my worries. Renting out serviced apartments instantly gives you a place to party and an excuse to invite people over.</p>
<p><strong>Nurture nature</strong></p>
<p>Nature is my sandbox. The mountains bring out the mountaineer in me. The rivers bring out the swimmer in me. The stars bring out the child in me. The great outdoors inspire me to unplug myself and just stand in awe at the marvel of creation. The bounties of nature are bestowed to people unconditionally and I do my best to give back by planting trees and living an eco-friendly life.</p>
<p>Not all those who wander are lost. Every journey I undertake makes me stronger as a person. It makes me who I am.</p>
]]>
      </content:encoded>
      <wfw:commentRss>https://www.staybazar.com/blog/index.php/2016/01/17/i-am-a-traveler/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
      <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>